[
    {
        "question": "Austria",
        "answer": "Vienna"
    },
    {
        "question": "Germany",
        "answer": "Berlin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Czech",
        "answer": "Prague"
    },
    {
        "question": "United Kingdom",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "France",
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "United States",
        "answer": "Washington D.C."
    },
    {
        "question": "Argentina",
        "answer": "Buenos Aires"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bolivia",
        "answer": "Sucre"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tanzania",
        "answer": "Dodoma"
    },
    {
        "question": "Japan",
        "answer": "Tokyo"
    }

]